[{"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/鱼缸.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/排球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/桌球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/皮球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/棒球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/篮球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子上面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/足球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [0], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图选一选", "stem": "选中桌子下面的物体。", "tableImg": "v2/通用/家具/桌子5.svg", "objectImg": ["v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/玻璃球.svg", "v2/通用/生活中的几何体/球体/地球.svg"], "position": [17, 12.8], "type": "pos-sequence-select3"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-5-2-01"}]